Evolutionary Surprise: Mighty Miniproteins Appeared “From Nowhere” - SciTechDaily﻿( James Webb telescope discovers ancient 'water world' in nearby star system - Livescience.com﻿( Gene Editing Gets a Triple Boost: “Happy Accident” Leads to Enhanced CRISPR Efficiency - SciTechDaily﻿( NASA Mars rover photos suggest ancient roaring river existed on Mars - Business Insider﻿( What Cassini's "Grand Finale" Taught Us About Saturn's Interior - Universe Today﻿( Largest-Ever Cosmic Explosion Has Raged for Years - Scientific American﻿( Physics - Testing Gravity's Effect on Quantum Spins - Physics﻿( Red planet page-turner? Scientists spot 'book' on Mars - msnNOW﻿( Scientists Just Spotted Something In Fruit Fly Cells Never Seen In Animals Before - IFLScience﻿( Betelgeuse Is Getting Brighter, Renewing Hopes for Supernova - ExtremeTech﻿( More than 50 people have tried to claim the $25K Maine meteorite reward - WGME﻿( Astronomers discover an unusually low-density super-Earth - Phys.org﻿( The Milky Way galaxy may be a different shape than we thought - Space.com﻿( Scientists record eerie sound in Earth's atmosphere they can't explain - Chron﻿( A New Subatomic Particle – The Most Beautiful Strongly Bound Dibaryon - SciTechDaily﻿( 62 New Moons Discovered Orbiting Saturn Using Innovative Astronomy - SciTechDaily﻿( Mastodon bones unearthed in Kent County to go on display - WOODTV.com﻿( Axiom Space Ax-2 private spaceflight: Live updates - Space.com﻿( Astronomers make groundbreaking discovery of first extrasolar radiation belt - ASU News Now﻿( Astronomers make groundbreaking discovery of first extrasolar radiation belt - ASU News Now﻿( Solar storm ALERT! Earth to suffer dangerous CME strike today, warns NOAA - HT Tech﻿( NASA's Lunar Flashlight to Fly by Earth - NASA﻿( James Webb telescope discovers ancient 'water world' in nearby star system - Livescience.com﻿( Neanderthals passed down their tall noses to modern humans, genetic analysis finds - Livescience.com﻿( A New Subatomic Particle – The Most Beautiful Strongly Bound Dibaryon - SciTechDaily﻿( Quantum Experiment Shows How Einstein Was Wrong About One Thing - ScienceAlert﻿( 62 New Moons Discovered Orbiting Saturn Using Innovative Astronomy - SciTechDaily﻿( Quantum physics proposes a new way to study biology – and the results could revolutionize our understanding of how life works - The Conversation Indonesia﻿( Groundbreaking study reveals strong and changeable magnetic field surrounding repeating fast radio burst - Interesting Engineering﻿( More than 50 people have tried to claim the $25K Maine meteorite reward - WGME﻿( The complicated history of how the Earth’s atmosphere became breathable - Ars Technica﻿( No killer asteroids heading our way for 1000 years. Probably - Metro.co.uk﻿( AI-powered DAGGER to give warning for CATASTROPHIC solar storms: NASA - HT Tech﻿( Scientists record eerie sound in Earth's atmosphere they can't explain - Chron﻿( Oh Hey, There's the JUICE Probe Heading for Jupiter - Gizmodo﻿( Gene Editing Gets a Triple Boost: “Happy Accident” Leads to Enhanced CRISPR Efficiency - SciTechDaily﻿( Scientists develop 3D ceramic printing without support - Interesting Engineering﻿( Scientists record eerie sound in Earth's atmosphere they can't explain - Chron﻿( More than 50 people have tried to claim the $25K Maine meteorite reward - WGME﻿( Oh Hey, There's the JUICE Probe Heading for Jupiter - Gizmodo﻿( Betelgeuse Is Getting Brighter, Renewing Hopes for Supernova - ExtremeTech﻿( A New Subatomic Particle – The Most Beautiful Strongly Bound Dibaryon - SciTechDaily﻿( Oxytocin's Role in Learning Birdsong Revealed - Neuroscience News﻿( Solar 'superflares' millions of times stronger than anything today may have sparked life on earth - Livescience.com﻿( Red planet page-turner? Scientists spot 'book' on Mars - msnNOW﻿( Opioid substitute buprenorphine is rarely misused: Medicare report - USA TODAY﻿( Researchers use AI to understand Alzheimer's disease, identify drug targets - Fox News﻿( Molecular Mechanism Key to Syncing Our Biological Clocks Discovered - Neuroscience News﻿( CDC urges mpox vaccination among people at high risk to prevent summer surge - CNBC﻿( Researchers develop new method to synthesize cannabis plant compound - Phys.org﻿( Dogs Get Dementia Too, Say Scientists — Here Are the Red Flags To Watch for in Your Senior Pet - Yahoo Life﻿( 6 Effective Ways to Use Walking to Get Lean and Shed Fat - BOXROX﻿( An AI Was Trained to Detect Parkinson's Years Before Symptoms Appeared - ScienceAlert﻿( Revisiting Folk Wisdom For Modern Chronic Wound Care - Hackaday﻿( Molecular Mechanism Key to Syncing Our Biological Clocks Discovered - Neuroscience News﻿( Hand Movements and Visual Attention: A Dance of Separate Rhythms - Neuroscience News﻿( 6 Effective Ways to Use Walking to Get Lean and Shed Fat - BOXROX﻿( A 27-year-old woman was told by an ER doctor she was having a panic attack. She later found out it was a stroke. - Yahoo News﻿( Statement on the antigen composition of COVID-19 vaccines - World Health Organization﻿( Scientists may have found an antidote for the world’s deadliest mushroom - South China Morning Post﻿( Single-Dose Rifapentine in Household Contacts of Patients with Leprosy | NEJM - nejm.org﻿( Products to Help With Menopause, Like Menopause Supplements - theSkimm﻿( 13 Reasons Your Hair Is Falling Out - Yahoo Life﻿( Myocarditis (acute infective) - United Kingdom - World Health Organization﻿( ‘I’m having a stroke but this couldn’t be me,’ Bryan Health nurse shares recovery after stroke - KOLN﻿( ‘I’m having a stroke but this couldn’t be me,’ Bryan Health nurse shares recovery after stroke - KOLN﻿( Good Vibrations: Tactile Stimulation May Aid Alzheimer's Treatment - Neuroscience News﻿( Regular Exercise Linked to Lower Parkinson’s Risk - Neuroscience News﻿( Opioid substitute buprenorphine is rarely misused: Medicare report - USA TODAY﻿( What happens during a heart attack? - Livescience.com﻿( As officials warn about possible summer rise in mpox, new studies show two doses of vaccine are better than one - CNN﻿( Opioid substitute buprenorphine is rarely misused: Medicare report - USA TODAY﻿( Myocarditis (acute infective) - United Kingdom - World Health Organization﻿( Is bird flu dangerous to humans and could it be the next pandemic? - The Times﻿( Scientists may have found an antidote for the world’s deadliest mushroom - South China Morning Post﻿( Dogs Get Dementia Too, Say Scientists — Here Are the Red Flags To Watch for in Your Senior Pet - Yahoo Life﻿( 40% of dementia cases caused by 12 modifiable lifestyle habits; Oxford experts share healthy tips - Indiatimes.com﻿( AI shown to predict risk of pancreatic cancer well before symptoms appear - Fox News﻿( The Best Bread For Gut Health, According to a Gastroenterologist - EatingWell﻿( Clock Out of Losing Sleep: A Simple and Effective Solution To Manage Insomnia - SciTechDaily﻿( 'Disorientation Device' to Prepare NASA Astronauts for Flight - Gizmodo﻿( Researchers use AI to understand Alzheimer's disease, identify drug targets - Fox News﻿( Genetic predisposition toward higher blood pressure, cholesterol may be linked to Alzheimer’s risk, study finds - CNN﻿( 40% of dementia cases caused by 12 modifiable lifestyle habits; Oxford experts share healthy tips - Indiatimes.com﻿( 6 Effective Ways to Use Walking to Get Lean and Shed Fat - BOXROX﻿( Yes, Your Water Can Go Bad - Lifehacker﻿( Identifying Pesticide Culprits in Parkinson’s Disease - Neuroscience News﻿( The WHO says we shouldn't bother with artificial sweeteners for weight loss or health. Is sugar better? - The Conversation﻿( Molecular “Superpower” of Antibiotic-Resistant Bacteria Revealed in New Research - SciTechDaily﻿( Weight loss drug reverses obesity for nearly half of teens in study - The Washington Post﻿( A Guide By Age for When to Get Mammograms, Colonoscopies and Other Screenings - The Wall Street Journal﻿( YouGov poll finds people are too tired to exercise or eat healthily - The Washington Post﻿( 12 Plants and Herbs That Naturally Repel Mosquitoes - Mosquito Repellent Plants - The Pioneer Woman﻿( 12 Plants and Herbs That Naturally Repel Mosquitoes - Mosquito Repellent Plants - The Pioneer Woman﻿( Ozempic Curbs Cancer Cells | HealthNews - Healthnews.com﻿( Genetic predisposition toward higher blood pressure, cholesterol may be linked to Alzheimer’s risk, study finds - CNN﻿( An AI Was Trained to Detect Parkinson's Years Before Symptoms Appeared - ScienceAlert﻿( Here’s why allergy season is getting longer in Dallas-Fort Worth - The Dallas Morning News﻿( Clock Out of Losing Sleep: A Simple and Effective Solution To Manage Insomnia - SciTechDaily﻿( Genetic predisposition toward higher blood pressure, cholesterol may be linked to Alzheimer’s risk, study finds - CNN﻿( Single-Dose Rifapentine in Household Contacts of Patients with Leprosy | NEJM - nejm.org﻿( Case 15-2023: A 33-Year-Old Man with Paresthesia of the Arms and Legs | NEJM - nejm.org﻿( Opioid substitute buprenorphine is rarely misused: Medicare report - USA TODAY﻿( Sexual dimorphism in the response to chronic circadian misalignment on a high-fat diet - Science﻿( Health officials warn of microscopic parasite causing intestinal illness in Georgia - WSB Atlanta﻿( Regular Exercise Linked to Lower Parkinson’s Risk - Neuroscience News﻿( 13 Reasons Your Hair Is Falling Out - Yahoo Life﻿( A Guide By Age for When to Get Mammograms, Colonoscopies and Other Screenings - The Wall Street Journal﻿( Sexual dimorphism in the response to chronic circadian misalignment on a high-fat diet - Science﻿( Is bird flu dangerous to humans and could it be the next pandemic? - The Times﻿( Ozempic Curbs Cancer Cells | HealthNews - Healthnews.com﻿( Comedy and Cognition: Unraveling Humor's Neural Nook - Neuroscience News﻿( Pain is by far the most common chronic ailment in America, study finds - Yahoo Sports﻿( Pain is by far the most common chronic ailment in America, study finds - Yahoo Sports﻿( Dogs Get Dementia Too, Say Scientists — Here Are the Red Flags To Watch for in Your Senior Pet - Yahoo Life﻿( 40% of dementia cases caused by 12 modifiable lifestyle habits; Oxford experts share healthy tips - Indiatimes.com﻿( Maine CDC reports death from exposure to rare tick-borne Powassan virus - Press Herald﻿( Products to Help With Menopause, Like Menopause Supplements - theSkimm﻿( Diabetes foot: Here's how diabetics can reduce the alarming burden of foot ulcers and amputations in Indi - Indiatimes.com﻿( 13 Reasons Your Hair Is Falling Out - Yahoo Life﻿( Single-Dose Rifapentine in Household Contacts of Patients with Leprosy | NEJM - nejm.org﻿( Placenta, Not Brain: Groundbreaking Study Shifts the Schizophrenia Narrative - SciTechDaily﻿( Anxious and avoidant attachment are elevated among individuals with eating disorders - PsyPost﻿( As officials warn about possible summer rise in mpox, new studies show two doses of vaccine are better than one - CNN﻿( Dogs Get Dementia Too, Say Scientists — Here Are the Red Flags To Watch for in Your Senior Pet - Yahoo Life﻿( 13 Reasons Your Hair Is Falling Out - Yahoo Life﻿( 12 Plants and Herbs That Naturally Repel Mosquitoes - Mosquito Repellent Plants - The Pioneer Woman﻿( Heart Transplants From Active COVID Donors Linked With Higher Mortality - Medpage Today﻿( Clock Out of Losing Sleep: A Simple and Effective Solution To Manage Insomnia - SciTechDaily﻿( Molecular “Superpower” of Antibiotic-Resistant Bacteria Revealed in New Research - SciTechDaily﻿( Lesbians, gay men face very different heart disease risks: US cardiac experts - New York Post ﻿( Single-Dose Rifapentine in Household Contacts of Patients with Leprosy | NEJM - nejm.org﻿( Identifying Pesticide Culprits in Parkinson’s Disease - Neuroscience News﻿( Dogs Get Dementia Too, Say Scientists — Here Are the Red Flags To Watch for in Your Senior Pet - Yahoo Life﻿( Products to Help With Menopause, Like Menopause Supplements - theSkimm﻿( Alzheimer's Pathology Reduced With 40 Hz Vibrations - Technology Networks﻿( A Guide By Age for When to Get Mammograms, Colonoscopies and Other Screenings - The Wall Street Journal﻿( AI shown to predict risk of pancreatic cancer well before symptoms appear - Fox News﻿( Genetic predisposition toward higher blood pressure, cholesterol may be linked to Alzheimer’s risk, study finds - CNN﻿( Good Vibrations: Tactile Stimulation May Aid Alzheimer's Treatment - Neuroscience News﻿( What happens during a heart attack? - Livescience.com﻿( 6 Effective Ways to Use Walking to Get Lean and Shed Fat - BOXROX﻿( Identifying Pesticide Culprits in Parkinson’s Disease - Neuroscience News﻿( A Guide By Age for When to Get Mammograms, Colonoscopies and Other Screenings - The Wall Street Journal﻿( Sexual dimorphism in the response to chronic circadian misalignment on a high-fat diet - Science﻿( Lesbians, gay men face very different heart disease risks: US cardiac experts - New York Post ﻿( An AI Was Trained to Detect Parkinson's Years Before Symptoms Appeared - ScienceAlert﻿( Alzheimer's Pathology Reduced With 40 Hz Vibrations - Technology Networks﻿( Australian woman with eczema reveals what you should never say to her - Daily Mail﻿( Comedy and Cognition: Unraveling Humor's Neural Nook - Neuroscience News﻿( Molecular Mechanism Key to Syncing Our Biological Clocks Discovered - Neuroscience News﻿( As officials warn about possible summer rise in mpox, new studies show two doses of vaccine are better than one - CNN﻿( How to eat yourself fit — the foods that boost muscles and stamina - The Times﻿( Good Vibrations: Tactile Stimulation May Aid Alzheimer's Treatment - Neuroscience News﻿( Are You Too Tired to Be Healthy? You Aren't Alone | Vantage with Palki Sharma - Firstpost﻿( The Biggest Etiquette Mistake At Hotel Breakfast Buffets - msnNOW﻿( Ozempic Curbs Cancer Cells | HealthNews - Healthnews.com﻿( Products to Help With Menopause, Like Menopause Supplements - theSkimm﻿( How Addictive Tech Hacks Your Brain - Gizmodo﻿( How Addictive Tech Hacks Your Brain - Gizmodo﻿( As officials warn about possible summer rise in mpox, new studies show two doses of vaccine are better than one - CNN﻿( 13 Reasons Your Hair Is Falling Out - Yahoo Life﻿( Dogs Get Dementia Too, Say Scientists — Here Are the Red Flags To Watch for in Your Senior Pet - Yahoo Life﻿( Single-Dose Rifapentine in Household Contacts of Patients with Leprosy | NEJM - nejm.org﻿( Researchers use AI to understand Alzheimer's disease, identify drug targets - Fox News﻿( Health officials warn of microscopic parasite causing intestinal illness in Georgia - WSB Atlanta﻿( Regular Exercise Linked to Lower Parkinson’s Risk - Neuroscience News﻿( Sexual dimorphism in the response to chronic circadian misalignment on a high-fat diet - Science﻿( 'We'll see them again': Last living Ray brother diagnosed with AIDS in 80s passes away - FOX 13 Tampa﻿( Hand Movements and Visual Attention: A Dance of Separate Rhythms - Neuroscience News﻿( Are You Too Tired to Be Healthy? You Aren't Alone | Vantage with Palki Sharma - Firstpost﻿( New study identifies structural brain differences in children with autism that are linked to language impairment - PsyPost﻿( Are You Too Tired to Be Healthy? You Aren't Alone | Vantage with Palki Sharma - Firstpost﻿( Are You Too Tired to Be Healthy? You Aren't Alone | Vantage with Palki Sharma - Firstpost﻿( What happens during a heart attack? - Livescience.com﻿( New study identifies structural brain differences in children with autism that are linked to language impairment - PsyPost﻿( What we all need to know about ultra-processed foods – but which science can't tell us yet - inews﻿( How to eat yourself fit — the foods that boost muscles and stamina - The Times﻿( Good Vibrations: Tactile Stimulation May Aid Alzheimer's Treatment - Neuroscience News﻿( Do YOU have 'tokophobia'? Study suggests 62% of women suffer from little-known condition - Daily Mail﻿( Molecular Mechanism Key to Syncing Our Biological Clocks Discovered - Neuroscience News﻿( Hand Movements and Visual Attention: A Dance of Separate Rhythms - Neuroscience News﻿( How the Brain Forgets: When Memory Lapses Become Fatal - Neuroscience News﻿( How Ozempic will change health and wellness marketing - AdAge.com﻿( Do YOU have 'tokophobia'? Study suggests 62% of women suffer from little-known condition - Daily Mail﻿( Researchers use AI to understand Alzheimer's disease, identify drug targets - Fox News﻿( Molecular Mechanism Key to Syncing Our Biological Clocks Discovered - Neuroscience News﻿( New Study Says Taking This Supplement Can Reverse Biological Age By a Year - The Everygirl﻿( Ancient kiss-tory: First lip lock likely took place in Middle East 4500 years ago - Study Finds﻿( A Universal Flu Vaccine Is Getting Closer to Reality - Gizmodo﻿( The Best Bread For Gut Health, According to a Gastroenterologist - EatingWell﻿( AI shown to predict risk of pancreatic cancer well before symptoms appear - Fox News﻿( 6 Effective Ways to Use Walking to Get Lean and Shed Fat - BOXROX﻿( 13 Reasons Your Hair Is Falling Out - Yahoo Life﻿( Post-COVID condition varies by variant and vaccination status - News-Medical.Net﻿( Health officials warn of microscopic parasite causing intestinal illness in Georgia - WSB Atlanta﻿( Heart Transplants From Active COVID Donors Linked With Higher Mortality - Medpage Today﻿( Sexual dimorphism in the response to chronic circadian misalignment on a high-fat diet - Science﻿( Past obesity can have lasting effects on mental health, study finds - The Guardian﻿( Neuroscience research links sleep problems to accelerated brain aging in older adults - PsyPost﻿( Good Vibrations: Tactile Stimulation May Aid Alzheimer's Treatment - Neuroscience News﻿( 40% of dementia cases caused by 12 modifiable lifestyle habits; Oxford experts share healthy tips - Indiatimes.com﻿( New study identifies structural brain differences in children with autism that are linked to language impairment - PsyPost﻿( Is bird flu dangerous to humans and could it be the next pandemic? - The Times﻿( Sexual dimorphism in the response to chronic circadian misalignment on a high-fat diet - Science﻿( Opioid substitute buprenorphine is rarely misused: Medicare report - USA TODAY﻿( Health officials warn of microscopic parasite causing intestinal illness in Georgia - WSB Atlanta﻿( Allergic to Eggs? Not These Eggs - Gizmodo﻿( Products to Help With Menopause, Like Menopause Supplements - theSkimm﻿( Opioid substitute buprenorphine is rarely misused: Medicare report - USA TODAY﻿( Why birds and their songs are good for our mental health - The Washington Post﻿( Pain is by far the most common chronic ailment in America, study finds - Yahoo Sports﻿( How to eat yourself fit — the foods that boost muscles and stamina - The Times﻿( Identifying Pesticide Culprits in Parkinson’s Disease - Neuroscience News﻿( How the Brain Forgets: When Memory Lapses Become Fatal - Neuroscience News﻿( Placenta, Not Brain: Groundbreaking Study Shifts the Schizophrenia Narrative - SciTechDaily﻿( Health officials warn of microscopic parasite causing intestinal illness in Georgia - WSB Atlanta﻿( Comparing Wegovy vs. Ozempic - Yahoo Life﻿( Vegan diet does not diminish nutrients in mothers' breastmilk - Medical News Today﻿( Clock Out of Losing Sleep: A Simple and Effective Solution To Manage Insomnia - SciTechDaily﻿( What is biotin? Foods to eat and if you should take it every day - USA TODAY﻿( Casual marijuana use in teens isn’t harmless. Here’s why experts say parents should be ‘very concerned.’ - AOL﻿( Dogs Get Dementia Too, Say Scientists — Here Are the Red Flags To Watch for in Your Senior Pet - Yahoo Life﻿( How the Brain Forgets: When Memory Lapses Become Fatal - Neuroscience News﻿( 12 Plants and Herbs That Naturally Repel Mosquitoes - Mosquito Repellent Plants - The Pioneer Woman﻿( Opioid substitute buprenorphine is rarely misused: Medicare report - USA TODAY﻿( What is biotin? Foods to eat and if you should take it every day - USA TODAY﻿( Are You Too Tired to Be Healthy? You Aren't Alone | Vantage with Palki Sharma - Firstpost﻿( Comedy and Cognition: Unraveling Humor's Neural Nook - Neuroscience News﻿( New Study Says Taking This Supplement Can Reverse Biological Age By a Year - The Everygirl﻿( Post-COVID condition varies by variant and vaccination status - News-Medical.Net﻿( Comedy and Cognition: Unraveling Humor's Neural Nook - Neuroscience News﻿( Hand Movements and Visual Attention: A Dance of Separate Rhythms - Neuroscience News﻿( Scientists Found a Drug That Relieves Daytime Sleepiness – And It's Not Caffeine - ScienceAlert﻿( How Addictive Tech Hacks Your Brain - Gizmodo﻿( Comparing Wegovy vs. Ozempic - Yahoo Life﻿( Identifying Pesticide Culprits in Parkinson’s Disease - Neuroscience News﻿( Why birds and their songs are good for our mental health - The Washington Post﻿( Alzheimer's Pathology Reduced With 40 Hz Vibrations - Technology Networks﻿( Opioid substitute buprenorphine is rarely misused: Medicare report - USA TODAY﻿( A 27-year-old woman was told by an ER doctor she was having a panic attack. She later found out it was a stroke. - Yahoo News﻿( Does Ozempic cause hair loss? Doctors reveal the truth about the drug's side effects - Woman & Home﻿( 13 Reasons Your Hair Is Falling Out - Yahoo Life﻿( 13 Reasons Your Hair Is Falling Out - Yahoo Life﻿( AI shown to predict risk of pancreatic cancer well before symptoms appear - Fox News﻿( The Cold Truth: Chilling Out in the Morning May Boost Fat Burning in Men - Neuroscience News﻿( Yes, Your Water Can Go Bad - Lifehacker﻿( Dogs Get Dementia Too, Say Scientists — Here Are the Red Flags To Watch for in Your Senior Pet - Yahoo Life﻿( Allergic to Eggs? Not These Eggs - Gizmodo﻿( Internet Use a Modifiable Dementia Risk Factor? - Medscape﻿( AI shown to predict risk of pancreatic cancer well before symptoms appear - Fox News﻿( Placenta, Not Brain: Groundbreaking Study Shifts the Schizophrenia Narrative - SciTechDaily﻿( What is biotin? Foods to eat and if you should take it every day - USA TODAY﻿( Health officials warn of microscopic parasite causing intestinal illness in Georgia - WSB Atlanta﻿( How close are we to an effective HIV vaccine? - PinkNews﻿( The Biggest Etiquette Mistake At Hotel Breakfast Buffets - msnNOW﻿( Do YOU have 'tokophobia'? Study suggests 62% of women suffer from little-known condition - Daily Mail﻿( Placenta, Not Brain: Groundbreaking Study Shifts the Schizophrenia Narrative - SciTechDaily﻿( 7 Worst Daily Habits for Your Joints as You Age - Eat This, Not That﻿( Placenta, Not Brain: Groundbreaking Study Shifts the Schizophrenia Narrative - SciTechDaily﻿( The Biggest Etiquette Mistake At Hotel Breakfast Buffets - msnNOW﻿( Anxious and avoidant attachment are elevated among individuals with eating disorders - PsyPost﻿( CDC did not say the polio vaccine gave millions of Americans a 'cancer virus' - The Associated Press﻿( Researchers develop new method to synthesize cannabis plant compound - Phys.org﻿( Australian woman with eczema reveals what you should never say to her - Daily Mail﻿( Lesbians, gay men face very different heart disease risks: US cardiac experts - New York Post ﻿( Ozempic Curbs Cancer Cells | HealthNews - Healthnews.com﻿( What illness did King George III have? - PBS NewsHour﻿( How to eat yourself fit — the foods that boost muscles and stamina - The Times﻿( Pain is by far the most common chronic ailment in America, study finds - Yahoo Sports﻿( What Your Weight at 60 Says About Your Health - AARP﻿( Heart Transplants From Active COVID Donors Linked With Higher Mortality - Medpage Today﻿( Post-COVID condition varies by variant and vaccination status - News-Medical.Net﻿( Good Vibrations: Tactile Stimulation May Aid Alzheimer's Treatment - Neuroscience News﻿( Are You Too Tired to Be Healthy? You Aren't Alone | Vantage with Palki Sharma - Firstpost﻿( As officials warn about possible summer rise in mpox, new studies show two doses of vaccine are better than one - CNN﻿( Why you really SHOULD be wary of wasps: Doctors warn stings can cause strokes - Daily Mail﻿( Casual marijuana use in teens isn’t harmless. Here’s why experts say parents should be ‘very concerned.’ - AOL﻿( Maine CDC reports death from exposure to rare tick-borne Powassan virus - Press Herald﻿( Scientists Found a Drug That Relieves Daytime Sleepiness – And It's Not Caffeine - ScienceAlert﻿( The Biggest Etiquette Mistake At Hotel Breakfast Buffets - msnNOW﻿( 7 Worst Daily Habits for Your Joints as You Age - Eat This, Not That﻿( 12 Plants and Herbs That Naturally Repel Mosquitoes - Mosquito Repellent Plants - The Pioneer Woman﻿( As officials warn about possible summer rise in mpox, new studies show two doses of vaccine are better than one - CNN﻿( What is biotin? Foods to eat and if you should take it every day - USA TODAY﻿( AI shown to predict risk of pancreatic cancer well before symptoms appear - Fox News﻿( Allergic to Eggs? Not These Eggs - Gizmodo﻿( Top 20 High-Protein Meats to Help You Build Muscle, Ranked - Yahoo Life﻿( Do YOU have 'tokophobia'? Study suggests 62% of women suffer from little-known condition - Daily Mail﻿( Sexual dimorphism in the response to chronic circadian misalignment on a high-fat diet - Science﻿( Identifying Pesticide Culprits in Parkinson’s Disease - Neuroscience News﻿( New study identifies structural brain differences in children with autism that are linked to language impairment - PsyPost﻿( What Your Weight at 60 Says About Your Health - AARP﻿( Molecular Mechanism Key to Syncing Our Biological Clocks Discovered - Neuroscience News﻿( The Biggest Etiquette Mistake At Hotel Breakfast Buffets - msnNOW﻿( Vegan diet does not diminish nutrients in mothers' breastmilk - Medical News Today﻿( CDC did not say the polio vaccine gave millions of Americans a 'cancer virus' - The Associated Press﻿( Diabetes foot: Here's how diabetics can reduce the alarming burden of foot ulcers and amputations in Indi - Indiatimes.com﻿( Internet Use a Modifiable Dementia Risk Factor? - Medscape﻿( How the Brain Forgets: When Memory Lapses Become Fatal - Neuroscience News﻿( Stroke death rates increased during the COVID pandemic, CDC says - Montgomery Advertiser﻿( 6 Effective Ways to Use Walking to Get Lean and Shed Fat - BOXROX﻿( Diabetes foot: Here's how diabetics can reduce the alarming burden of foot ulcers and amputations in Indi - Indiatimes.com﻿( Case 15-2023: A 33-Year-Old Man with Paresthesia of the Arms and Legs | NEJM - nejm.org﻿( A Guide By Age for When to Get Mammograms, Colonoscopies and Other Screenings - The Wall Street Journal﻿( How the Brain Forgets: When Memory Lapses Become Fatal - Neuroscience News﻿( 6 Smart Ways to Slash Your Cancer Risk Right Now - Men's Health﻿( Lesbians, gay men face very different heart disease risks: US cardiac experts - New York Post ﻿( Placenta, Not Brain: Groundbreaking Study Shifts the Schizophrenia Narrative - SciTechDaily﻿( Ozempic Curbs Cancer Cells | HealthNews - Healthnews.com﻿( 6 Smart Ways to Slash Your Cancer Risk Right Now - Men's Health﻿( Alzheimer's Pathology Reduced With 40 Hz Vibrations - Technology Networks﻿( Neuroscience research links sleep problems to accelerated brain aging in older adults - PsyPost﻿( Single-Dose Rifapentine in Household Contacts of Patients with Leprosy | NEJM - nejm.org﻿( Past obesity can have lasting effects on mental health, study finds - The Guardian﻿( Post-COVID condition varies by variant and vaccination status - News-Medical.Net﻿( Pain is by far the most common chronic ailment in America, study finds - Yahoo Sports﻿( 12 Plants and Herbs That Naturally Repel Mosquitoes - Mosquito Repellent Plants - The Pioneer Woman﻿( Internet Use a Modifiable Dementia Risk Factor? - Medscape﻿( 12 Plants and Herbs That Naturally Repel Mosquitoes - Mosquito Repellent Plants - The Pioneer Woman﻿( Humanity's earliest recorded kiss occurred in Mesopotamia 4,500 years ago, claims new study - Phys.org﻿( 'We'll see them again': Last living Ray brother diagnosed with AIDS in 80s passes away - FOX 13 Tampa﻿( Allergic to Eggs? Not These Eggs - Gizmodo﻿( What happens during a heart attack? - Livescience.com﻿( Indian-Led Team In US Discovers "Pathbreaking" Treatment For Brain Cancer - NDTV﻿( Australian woman with eczema reveals what you should never say to her - Daily Mail﻿( Stroke death rates increased during the COVID pandemic, CDC says - Montgomery Advertiser﻿( Is bird flu dangerous to humans and could it be the next pandemic? - The Times﻿( Vegan diet does not diminish nutrients in mothers' breastmilk - Medical News Today﻿( Alzheimer's Pathology Reduced With 40 Hz Vibrations - Technology Networks﻿( A Universal Flu Vaccine Is Getting Closer to Reality - Gizmodo﻿( New Study Says Taking This Supplement Can Reverse Biological Age By a Year - The Everygirl﻿( New study identifies structural brain differences in children with autism that are linked to language impairment - PsyPost﻿( A Guide By Age for When to Get Mammograms, Colonoscopies and Other Screenings - The Wall Street Journal﻿( Regular Exercise Linked to Lower Parkinson’s Risk - Neuroscience News﻿( Anxious and avoidant attachment are elevated among individuals with eating disorders - PsyPost﻿( Vaccine Effectiveness of JYNNEOS against Mpox Disease in the United States | NEJM - nejm.org﻿( 40% of dementia cases caused by 12 modifiable lifestyle habits; Oxford experts share healthy tips - Indiatimes.com﻿( I'm a dentist — these 5 foods are awful for your teeth - New York Post ﻿( Pain is by far the most common chronic ailment in America, study finds - Yahoo Sports﻿( How close are we to an effective HIV vaccine? - PinkNews﻿( What Your Weight at 60 Says About Your Health - AARP﻿( Molecular Mechanism Key to Syncing Our Biological Clocks Discovered - Neuroscience News﻿( I'm a dentist — these 5 foods are awful for your teeth - New York Post ﻿( How Addictive Tech Hacks Your Brain - Gizmodo﻿( Humanity's earliest recorded kiss occurred in Mesopotamia 4,500 years ago, claims new study - Phys.org﻿ In new letter, Janet Yellen warns Speaker McCarthy US will breach debt limit June 1 - Fox Business﻿ SEC Emails Suggest XRP Is Not Security, SHIB Scores New Listing, ADA to Reach $500 Billion Market Cap, Says Crypto Capital Venture CEO: Crypto News Digest by U.Today - U.Today﻿ Minneapolis Fed President Neel Kashkari: Close call whether to raise or pause rates in June - CNBC Television﻿ PacWest shares jump after $2.6 bln real estate loan sale - Reuters﻿ Major companies lack protections for free speech, religion: study | U.S. News - The Christian Post﻿ Fears of AI hitting black market stir concerns of criminals evading government regulations: Expert - Fox News﻿ Chevron announces $6.3 billion deal to acquire Denver-based PDC Energy - The Denver Post﻿ Biglaw Merger Alert: Shearman & Sterling Announces Plans To Combine With Allen & Overy - Above the Law﻿ Startup founder Charlie Javice pleads not guilty to defrauding JPMorgan - New York Post ﻿ Seattle Amazon workers plan walkout over return to office, layoffs - The Seattle Times﻿ Oil Prices Sink As Fears Of A U.S. Default Continue To Weigh On Markets - OilPrice.com﻿ Amazon founder Jeff Bezos is reportedly engaged to Lauren Sanchez - The Seattle Times﻿ Meta fined $1.3bn over transfer of EU user data to the US - Al Jazeera English﻿ Startup founder Charlie Javice pleads not guilty to defrauding JPMorgan - New York Post ﻿ California has a new $7.3B plan to fix its transmission problems - Canary Media﻿ Amazon founder Jeff Bezos is reportedly engaged to Lauren Sanchez - The Seattle Times﻿ $100 Million Google Deal Could Change the Way You Use a Computer - TheStreet﻿ Startup founder Charlie Javice pleads not guilty to defrauding JPMorgan - New York Post ﻿ Debt-Ceiling Stalemate Leaves Investors Waiting - Bloomberg﻿ PacWest shares jump after $2.6 bln real estate loan sale - Reuters﻿ The State of Fashion Special Edition | The New Face of Beauty - The Business of Fashion﻿ $100 Million Google Deal Could Change the Way You Use a Computer - TheStreet﻿ Stock futures are up slightly as Wall Street watches for debt ceiling progress: Live updates - CNBC﻿ Treasury could issue $700 billion in T-bills within weeks of a debt deal - Markets Insider﻿ Celebrating Bitcoin Pizza Day: the Time a Bitcoin User Bought 2 Pizzas for 10,000 BTC - CoinDesk﻿ Inflation pummeled US household finances last year, Fed survey finds - Fox Business﻿ Biglaw Merger Alert: Shearman & Sterling Announces Plans To Combine With Allen & Overy - Above the Law﻿ Debt ceiling: Yellen says Treasury to run out of funds by ‘early June’ and possibly ‘June 1’ - The Hill﻿ Ford strikes lithium deals in bid to secure EV battery supplies - Financial Times﻿ Minneapolis Fed President Neel Kashkari: Close call whether to raise or pause rates in June - CNBC Television﻿ Treasury could issue $700 billion in T-bills within weeks of a debt deal - Markets Insider﻿ Major companies lack protections for free speech, religion: study | U.S. News - The Christian Post﻿ China bans Micron Chips, saying they pose a 'national security risk' - Yahoo Finance﻿ Celebrating Bitcoin Pizza Day: the Time a Bitcoin User Bought 2 Pizzas for 10,000 BTC - CoinDesk﻿ Debt ceiling negotiations will be really hard, says Evercore's Roger Altman - CNBC Television﻿ Treasury could issue $700 billion in T-bills within weeks of a debt deal - Markets Insider﻿ Ford strikes lithium deals in bid to secure EV battery supplies - Financial Times﻿ Ford strikes lithium deals in bid to secure EV battery supplies - Financial Times﻿ Gen Z isn't afraid of unemployment, Suzy Welch says - Business Insider﻿ Debt-Ceiling Stalemate Leaves Investors Waiting - Bloomberg﻿ Biglaw Merger Alert: Shearman & Sterling Announces Plans To Combine With Allen & Overy - Above the Law﻿ Seattle Amazon workers plan walkout over return to office, layoffs - The Seattle Times﻿ Minneapolis Fed President Neel Kashkari: Close call whether to raise or pause rates in June - CNBC Television﻿ NASH Drugs Suffer Another Blow, but Hope Remains - Barron's﻿ More than 150 Republicans unite to condemn Biden's 'ill-considered' electric vehicle push - Fox News﻿ California has a new $7.3B plan to fix its transmission problems - Canary Media﻿ Uber's diversity chief on leave after employee criticism over 'Don't Call Me Karen' panel - CNN﻿ Japan's Mizuho expands in US banking with $550 mln Greenhill deal - Reuters﻿ PacWest shares jump after $2.6 bln real estate loan sale - Reuters﻿ Treasury could issue $700 billion in T-bills within weeks of a debt deal - Markets Insider﻿ Manhattan BP rolls out MSG and Penn Station plan, backs 8th Ave. overhaul - New York Post ﻿ JPMorgan plans 'unmatched' $15.7bn spending spree on new initiatives - Financial Times﻿ After Tesla snub, Oklahoma lands a 3 GW solar factory - Electrek.co﻿ Nike stock could take a hit as Foot Locker stumbles, analysts say - Yahoo Finance﻿ As Bezos wins NASA contract to race Musk to put man on the Moon, the dark side of their 20-year feud - Daily Mail﻿ More than 150 Republicans unite to condemn Biden's 'ill-considered' electric vehicle push - Fox News﻿ Startup founder Charlie Javice pleads not guilty to defrauding JPMorgan - New York Post ﻿ Gold, silver pressured by bearish charts, outside markets - Kitco NEWS﻿ Fed presidents signal more interest rate hikes needed to cool inflation - Fox Business﻿ Bill Gates says the best AI agent will replace search and shopping websites - Fox Business﻿ Memorial Day daytrips: DC-area hikes, outdoor activities worth your time - WTOP﻿ $100 Million Google Deal Could Change the Way You Use a Computer - TheStreet﻿ PacWest shares jump after $2.6 bln real estate loan sale - Reuters﻿ Gold, silver pressured by bearish charts, outside markets - Kitco NEWS﻿ JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon on how to get his job: 'Give a s--t' - Fox Business﻿ China bans Micron Chips, saying they pose a 'national security risk' - Yahoo Finance﻿ The 15 Best Kitchen Deals Happening at Target This Memorial Day Weekend - Food & Wine﻿ Buy the dip? If the debt ceiling isn't resolved soon, markets will likely slide - CNN﻿ Here’s what Pfizer and Moderna say is next for their Covid vaccines - CNBC﻿ The Treasury Department could issue $700 billion in T-bills within weeks of a debt-ceiling deal, draining liquidity from markets - Yahoo Finance﻿ Amazon founder Jeff Bezos is reportedly engaged to Lauren Sanchez - The Seattle Times﻿ Ripple v. SEC: Crypto Lawyer Makes Startling Prediction as Case Resolution Nears - U.Today﻿ Photos: Amazon HQ2’s first phase is basically complete - ARLnow﻿ First Mover Asia: Bitcoin Holds Steady Near $27K as Investors Weigh Debt Ceiling Developments - CoinDesk﻿ Yellen triples down on debt ceiling deadline - Axios﻿ Gen Z isn't afraid of unemployment, Suzy Welch says - Business Insider﻿ NASH Drugs Suffer Another Blow, but Hope Remains - Barron's﻿ Yellen triples down on debt ceiling deadline - Axios﻿ Nvidia Stock Revisits ATHs, Why Bitcoin Could Be Next | Bitcoinist.com - Bitcoinist﻿ The first all-electric Escalade joins Cadillac’s EV lineup later this year - Engadget﻿ Kioxia BG6 Series M.2 2230 PCIe 4.0 SSD Lineup Adds BiCS6 to the Mix - AnandTech﻿ Kioxia BG6 Series M.2 2230 PCIe 4.0 SSD Lineup Adds BiCS6 to the Mix - AnandTech﻿ First Mover Asia: Bitcoin Holds Steady Near $27K as Investors Weigh Debt Ceiling Developments - CoinDesk﻿ Pfizer Stock Jumps After Oral Drug Outperforms Novo Superstar Ozempic In Weight Loss | Investor's Business Daily - Investor's Business Daily﻿ Ford CEO Jim Farley says automaker has vision to execute change - Detroit Free Press﻿ Zoom lifts annual forecasts even as growth slows from pandemic peaks - Reuters﻿ The Treasury Department could issue $700 billion in T-bills within weeks of a debt-ceiling deal, draining liquidity from markets - Yahoo Finance﻿ Photos: Amazon HQ2’s first phase is basically complete - ARLnow﻿ Subtle Hint of New Bitcoin and Ethereum Bull Runs Showing Up On-Chain, Says Analytics Firm Santiment - The Daily Hodl﻿ Fears of AI hitting black market stir concerns of criminals evading government regulations: Expert - Fox News﻿ After less than a decade, Rehbergs close Montana fast-food restaurants - Q2 News﻿ Here’s what Pfizer and Moderna say is next for their Covid vaccines - CNBC﻿ Manhattan BP rolls out MSG and Penn Station plan, backs 8th Ave. overhaul - New York Post ﻿ Inflation pummeled US household finances last year, Fed survey finds - Fox Business﻿ Minneapolis Fed President Neel Kashkari: Close call whether to raise or pause rates in June - CNBC Television﻿ Novartis to buy Avrobio gene therapy for $88M, leaving rest of the biotech on the shelf - FierceBiotech﻿ The State of Fashion Special Edition | The New Face of Beauty - The Business of Fashion﻿ Debt ceiling negotiations will be really hard, says Evercore's Roger Altman - CNBC Television﻿ The State of Fashion Special Edition | The New Face of Beauty - The Business of Fashion﻿ Xcel Energy holds groundbreaking ceremony for Sherco Solar project - KSTP﻿ Subtle Hint of New Bitcoin and Ethereum Bull Runs Showing Up On-Chain, Says Analytics Firm Santiment - The Daily Hodl﻿ Novartis to buy Avrobio gene therapy for $88M, leaving rest of the biotech on the shelf - FierceBiotech﻿ Oil Prices Sink As Fears Of A U.S. Default Continue To Weigh On Markets - OilPrice.com﻿ Nvidia Stock Revisits ATHs, Why Bitcoin Could Be Next | Bitcoinist.com - Bitcoinist﻿ Fed presidents signal more interest rate hikes needed to cool inflation - Fox Business﻿ Michigan gas prices see large spike ahead of Memorial Day weekend - WXYZ 7 Action News Detroit﻿ OpenAI leaders propose international regulatory body for AI - TechCrunch﻿ Seattle Amazon workers plan walkout over return to office, layoffs - The Seattle Times﻿ EU Regulators Hit Meta with Record $1.3 Billion Fine for Data Transfer Violations - The Hacker News﻿ OpenAI leaders propose international regulatory body for AI - TechCrunch﻿ Celebrating Bitcoin Pizza Day: the Time a Bitcoin User Bought 2 Pizzas for 10,000 BTC - CoinDesk﻿ Blueprint's Ayvakit picks up long-awaited label expansion - FiercePharma﻿ Nike stock could take a hit as Foot Locker stumbles, analysts say - Yahoo Finance﻿ $100 Million Google Deal Could Change the Way You Use a Computer - TheStreet﻿ Gen Z isn't afraid of unemployment, Suzy Welch says - Business Insider﻿ Blueprint's Ayvakit picks up long-awaited label expansion - FiercePharma﻿ OpenAI leaders propose international regulatory body for AI - TechCrunch﻿ Walmart just dropped 50+ can't-miss early Memorial Day deals, starting at $8 - Yahoo Life﻿ Uber's diversity chief on leave after employee criticism over 'Don't Call Me Karen' panel - CNN﻿ JPMorgan CEO Jamie Dimon on how to get his job: 'Give a s--t' - Fox Business﻿ Gen Z isn't afraid of unemployment, Suzy Welch says - Business Insider﻿ Blueprint's Ayvakit picks up long-awaited label expansion - FiercePharma﻿ After less than a decade, Rehbergs close Montana fast-food restaurants - Q2 News﻿ Nvidia Stock Revisits ATHs, Why Bitcoin Could Be Next | Bitcoinist.com - Bitcoinist﻿ $100 Million Google Deal Could Change the Way You Use a Computer - TheStreet﻿ Amazon One launches age verification for beer, alcohol purchases - About Amazon﻿ Jeff Bezos and Lauren Sánchez are engaged - CNN﻿ Yellen Says It's Now 'Highly Likely' US Out of Cash Early June - Bloomberg﻿ Amazon One launches age verification for beer, alcohol purchases - About Amazon﻿ Nvidia Stock Revisits ATHs, Why Bitcoin Could Be Next | Bitcoinist.com - Bitcoinist﻿ Nike stock could take a hit as Foot Locker stumbles, analysts say - Yahoo Finance﻿ Fed Ready to Move But Will Pause, Economist Swonk Says - Bloomberg Television﻿ Seattle Amazon workers plan walkout over return to office, layoffs - The Seattle Times﻿ Uber's diversity chief on leave after employee criticism over 'Don't Call Me Karen' panel - CNN﻿ As Bezos wins NASA contract to race Musk to put man on the Moon, the dark side of their 20-year feud - Daily Mail﻿ Treasury could issue $700 billion in T-bills within weeks of a debt deal - Markets Insider﻿ GM Quietly Builds Shiny Tesla Killers - TheStreet﻿ Treasury could issue $700 billion in T-bills within weeks of a debt deal - Markets Insider﻿ JPMorgan plans 'unmatched' $15.7bn spending spree on new initiatives - Financial Times﻿ China bans Micron Chips, saying they pose a 'national security risk' - Yahoo Finance﻿ Madison still plans to sue Kia and Hyundai despite recent federal class-action settlement, city attorney says - Channel3000.com - WISC-TV3﻿ Pfizer Stock Jumps After Oral Drug Outperforms Novo Superstar Ozempic In Weight Loss | Investor's Business Daily - Investor's Business Daily﻿ Yellen triples down on debt ceiling deadline - Axios﻿ World’s most expensive ice cream from Japan costs more than $6,000 per serving - Yahoo! Voices﻿ Apple Stock Downgraded On Signs Of Slowing iPhone Demand - Investor's Business Daily﻿ PacWest shares jump after $2.6 bln real estate loan sale - Reuters﻿ NASH Drugs Suffer Another Blow, but Hope Remains - Barron's﻿ NASH Drugs Suffer Another Blow, but Hope Remains - Barron's﻿ Treasury could issue $700 billion in T-bills within weeks of a debt deal - Markets Insider﻿ Startup founder Charlie Javice pleads not guilty to defrauding JPMorgan - New York Post ﻿ Nike stock could take a hit as Foot Locker stumbles, analysts say - Yahoo Finance﻿ Startup founder Charlie Javice pleads not guilty to defrauding JPMorgan - New York Post ﻿ Novartis to buy Avrobio gene therapy for $88M, leaving rest of the biotech on the shelf - FierceBiotech﻿ An inside look at Uber's new feature for the next generation of riders - GMA﻿ Chevron announces $6.3 billion deal to acquire Denver-based PDC Energy - The Denver Post﻿ Asia markets mixed as U.S. debt ceiling talks end with no deal - CNBC﻿ The State of Fashion Special Edition | The New Face of Beauty - The Business of Fashion﻿ An inside look at Uber's new feature for the next generation of riders - GMA﻿ ‘The momentum in the housing market has shifted to the Sun Belt’: 5 hottest metros are in the South - MarketWatch﻿ After less than a decade, Rehbergs close Montana fast-food restaurants - Q2 News﻿ Oil Prices Sink As Fears Of A U.S. Default Continue To Weigh On Markets - OilPrice.com﻿ Asia markets mixed as U.S. debt ceiling talks end with no deal - CNBC﻿ The State of Fashion Special Edition | The New Face of Beauty - The Business of Fashion﻿ ChatGPT makers say AI could surpass humanity within 10 years - Business Insider﻿ The Debt-Ceiling Fight Bores the Stock Market. That Could Change Fast. - Barron's﻿ Virgin Orbit auctions $36 mln in remaining assets as company folds - Reuters﻿ PacWest Sells Real-Estate Lending Unit - WSJ - The Wall Street Journal﻿ US new home sales, business activity rise to 13-month highs - Reuters﻿ JP Morgan claims US Virgin Islands 'complicit' in Jeffrey Epstein crimes - The Guardian US﻿ Can the world come together to avoid more crypto scandals? | DW News - DW News﻿ Speeding Tesla driver dies after colliding with 9 vehicles in New Haven - WTNH.com﻿ FDA Approves New Buprenorphine Treatment Option for Opioid Use Disorder - FDA.gov﻿ New plan to change food labels - ABC News﻿ Why This Coronavirus Star's Rebound Will Take Longer Than Hoped - Investor's Business Daily﻿ Energy Dept. rejects $200M grant to battery maker after GOP criticism over alleged ties to China - The Associated Press﻿ Amazon corporate workers plan walkout next week over return-to-office policies - CNN﻿ Meta New Round of Layoffs to Impact Partnerships, Business Divisions - Business Insider﻿ Gold, silver down as greenback bulls flex their muscles - Kitco NEWS﻿ BlackRock bond chief Rieder says U.S. economy in 'much better shape’ than doomsayers say - CNBC﻿ Former Fed Chair Ben Bernanke says there's more work ahead to control inflation - CNBC﻿ Cracker Barrel closed in Jackson - WAPT Jackson﻿ Former Fed Chair Ben Bernanke says there's more work ahead to control inflation - CNBC﻿ Major Mass., NH health insurance provider Point32Health says customer data compromised - WCVB Boston﻿ Rajiv Jain-Led GQG Partners Adani Bet Has Already Gained Rs 9,000 Crore - BQ Prime﻿ More than 400,000 Waffle Makers Are Being Recalled — Here's Why | Kitchn - The Kitchn﻿ Stock futures are little changed as investors eye debt ceiling clash in Washington: Live updates - CNBC﻿ Cracker Barrel closed in Jackson - WAPT Jackson﻿ India RBI chief flags governance gaps, stressed assets misreporting at some banks - Reuters﻿ Markets are sounding alarms on China's economy, but analysts say Wall Street is missing the big picture - Yahoo Finance﻿ Tesla CEO Elon Musk expected to visit China this week, meet officials - sources - Yahoo Finance﻿ Dogecoin Chart Pattern Suggests Volatility Explosion Ahead - CoinDesk﻿ Japan's Nikkei share average rises to highest since July 1990 - Reuters﻿ India RBI chief flags governance gaps, stressed assets misreporting at some banks - Reuters﻿ Japan's Nikkei share average rises to highest since July 1990 - Reuters﻿ For the first time, more money is going into solar power than oil - CBS News﻿ Gold price trades below $1950 ahead of Congress debt ceiling vote and June Fed decision - Kitco NEWS﻿ NVIDIA is upgrading the in-car experience with AI, streaming, and advanced safety features - Electrek.co﻿ Tesla CEO Elon Musk expected to visit China this week, meet officials - sources - Yahoo Finance﻿ Futures Rise On Debt Deal; Tesla, Nvidia In Focus - Investor's Business Daily﻿ State Farm won't insure new California customers amid wildfire risks - Axios﻿ Billionaire Jack Dorsey Says America Has a Problem. Elon Musk Names It - TheStreet﻿ Arby's employee found dead in freezer had 'beat her hands bloody' trying to escape, lawsuit says - Fox Business﻿ Major central banks were expected to pause rate hikes soon. Now it's not so clear cut - CNBC﻿ NVIDIA: Grace Hopper Has Entered Full Production & Announcing DGX GH200 AI Supercomputer - AnandTech﻿ The Decarbonization Agenda: Carbon Neutral by 2035 - Times of India﻿ Food delivery fees add up. Who keeps the money from all those surcharges? - The Hill